<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CollegeSuperApp</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_myaccount">My Account</string>
    <string name="title_events">Events</string>
    <string name="upcoming_events"> Upcoming Events </string>
    <string name="desc"><![CDATA[The Google Solution Challenge is an annual competition that encourages students to develop innovative solutions using Google technologies. Whether you\'re passionate about web development, machine learning, mobile apps, or anything in between, this challenge is your chance to make a real-world impact. ðŸŒ What to Expect at the Info Session: Learn about the Google Solution Challenge guidelines and requirements. Get insights into past successful projects and their impact. Discover resources and tools available for your project development. Hear tips and advice from experienced mentors. Have your questions answered during the Q&A session. ðŸŽ‰ Why Participate: Showcase your skills to a global audience. Collaborate with like-minded students and industry professionals. Stand a chance to win exciting prizes and Google Cloud credits. Make a positive impact by solving real-world challenges. ðŸš€ How to Join: Don\'t miss this chance to be part of a community of innovators and problem solvers. Mark your calendar and get ready to embark on a journey of creativity, collaboration, and impact! If you have any questions, feel free to reach out. We look forward to seeing you at the Info Session! Hope to see you there!The Google Solution Challenge is an annual competition that encourages students to develop innovative solutions using Google technologies. Whether you\'re passionate about web development, machine learning, mobile apps, or anything in between, this challenge is your chance to make a real-world impact. ðŸŒ What to Expect at the Info Session: Learn about the Google Solution Challenge guidelines and requirements. Get insights into past successful projects and their impact. Discover resources and tools available for your project development. Hear tips and advice from experienced mentors. Have your questions answered during the Q&A session. ðŸŽ‰ Why Participate: Showcase your skills to a global audience. Collaborate with like-minded students and industry professionals. Stand a chance to win exciting prizes and Google Cloud credits. Make a positive impact by solving real-world challenges. ðŸš€ How to Join: Don\'t miss this chance to be part of a community of innovators and problem solvers. Mark your calendar and get ready to embark on a journey of creativity, collaboration, and impact! If you have any questions, feel free to reach out. We look forward to seeing you at the Info Session! Hope to see you there!]]></string>

</resources>